lovein90days.com 2018-11-22

# Privacy Policy - Love in 90 Days

Last Updated and Effective as of: May 25, 2018

Love in 90 Days (“Company,” “we” or “us”) has created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting your information. Our business is based on adding value to your life through blogs, emails, newsletters, mentoring, and online products. Most importantly we do not sell, rent or trade our email lists with other companies. 

We keep the minimum information as possible that allows us to add value to your life. 

This Privacy Policy goes into detail on the information we collect, how and why we use it and how we keep it secure. This policy applies to information we collect on the Website and in email, text, or other electronic messages between you and the Website.

This Privacy Policy governs your access to and use of Lovein90Days.com, including any content, functionality and services offered on or through Lovein90Days.com (the “Website“), whether as a guest or a registered user.

Please read the Privacy Policy carefully before you start to use the Website. By using the Website or by clicking to accept or agree to the Terms of Use when this option is made available to you, you accept and agree to be bound and abide by the Privacy Policy.

**What Information Do We Collect?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. We shall always ask you to provide only a minimum data which is needed for completing the service you asked for. Before leaving your data you will be clearly and intelligibly explained the purpose of collecting your data and asked to give your consent to it, which you can also withdraw easily.

**  
What Do We Use Information For?**  
We only collect the minimum information appropriate to deliver to you the service you are accessing and we only ever use this information to better understand your needs and provide you with a better service.

So, we use this information for the following:  
• To personalize your experience To deliver our products and services  
• To improve our products, services and website  
• To periodically send emails about products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting and beneficial using the email address you have provided  
• Internal record keeping 

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**Do We Disclose Any Information to Outside Parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we are required to comply by law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**How Do We Protect Your Information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

**Opt Out and GDPR**  
We provide opportunities to unsubscribe/opt-out from our Services in all newsletters and marketing emails and you may choose to do so at any time.

If you live in the European Union, you may also use the unsubscribe/opt-out features to request that we redact your personal information from our records. We will comply within a reasonable time and, in any case, within the time limits established by applicable law. We may ask you for additional information to verify your identity. In some cases, however, we may limit or deny your request if the law permits or requires us to do so or if we are unable to verify your identify. 

If you need further assistance with unsubscribing or opting-out of any of the Services, or with redaction of your personal information, please email customer service at customerservice@lovein90days.com for assistance. Please note that we may not be able to remove your information from the records of any third parties who have received your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

At our discretion, we may determine that your lack of engagement in the Services indicates your desire to opt-out of the Services. For example, you may be removed from our email list if you have not opened an email from us for a certain period of time. You may opt-in again at any time. 

**Do We Use Cookies?**  
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. However, if you still do not want us to place cookies to your computers, you may set your browser not to accept cookies.

**How Long Do We Keep Your Information?**  
We will retain your information indefinitely until you opt-out, request removal or redaction, or we choose to remove it.

**Privacy of Children**  
We are in compliance with the requirements of the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. The Sites are not directed to children under the age of 13 and therefore we will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13.

We require users under 18 to obtain the consent of a parent or guardian to view the Sites. You agree to abide by any such restrictions and not to help anyone avoid these restrictions.

**Security Policy**  
By using the Website, you assume the risk of an unauthorized security beach. Even though we take prudent and reasonable measures to secure your personal information, our servers, and our physical premises, we cannot guaranty that our efforts will be completely effective.

**Consent to Transfer**  
The Site is operated from the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By using our Sites, participating in any of the Services and/or providing us with your information, you consent to this transfer.

**  
Changes in Site Ownership**  
In the event of a merger, acquisition, or sale of any of our assets or the Sites you consent to the disclosure to, and use by, any subsequent owner or operator of the Sites, of any information about you contained in our databases.
